你知道他们在争论些什么吗
Do you have any idea what they were arguing about?
你...你会讲英文吗
D-Do you speak English?
我会  抱歉  我的德文不太好
Yeah. No, I'm sorry. My German is not very good.
你听没听过这个说法
Have you heard that as couples get older,
夫妻会逐渐失去听到对方声音的能力
they lose their ability to hear each other?
没听说过
No.
据说男人会渐渐听不到高音
Well,supposedly,men lose their ability to hear higher-pitched sounds.
而女人会渐渐听不到低音
And women eventually lose hearing on the low end.
-算是把对方屏蔽了  -算是吧
- I guess they sort of nullify each other. - I guess.
大自然就是这么让伴侣们
Nature's way of allowing couples
不要杀掉对方  厮守到老的
to grow old together without killing each other.
你在读什么书
What are you reading?
艾德沃达夫人  死者  眼睛的历史
这本啊
Ah, yeah.
你呢
How about you?